Today is Asha's birthday, how can we
impress her by
talking on a video call?
What are you doing, Asha? What are you doing listening to us like this?
Today is your birthday, or should we
celebrate? When
Jai's voice speaks, a ghost voice comes in. If you are
happy for a while, don't be upset. What are you saying?
Hello, what
are you saying? Who are you talking about? Is
that Mano Raja, stupid fellow?
Okay, don't leave yet. Don't leave yet.
I told you to get an appointment with the doctor at four o'clock.
What did you forget in the morning?
Otherwise, I work so hard at the office that I
can't even go out for two hours.  Please
understand, what are you doing? Go and get your mother. It's
been two years since our mother died. When we
got home [laughter], it was
torn apart. It's been two years since your father died.  You may have gone with your father
.  If you're in a hurry for a while,
you'll disturb everything.
Excuse me, sir.
Hey, come in,
sir.   You're
already here, you stupid
costin' idiots.
Sir, you are very angry.
Can you make a vibe call, sir?  No, Asha didn't call,
sir.
Okay, okay, okay,
Asha Business, all of it, all of it,
50,000.
I have put Asha Pearl in the middle.
Big deposit, sir.   That's good,
I'll send all the account details on WhatsApp.  This
matter should not be revealed.  Because
you are the manager of this office.  There are some
things you can't do yourself, sir.
Without that, you
have an image of yourself in this office.
Very good job, right now you go out.
Okay, sir.
You stand
sir, you go
sir.
Hey you stand you go lie down,
oh this spoken English guy is a complete idiot, he does
n't want to work for a car company.  Who should I give this to, sir?
Mind your words, Mr. Manio.
Who should I give this to, sir?
Sir, I should give it to Asha as a gift, but I don't want her to
know about it.   They
pay me a pittance for this kind of work. What's
nothing sir? Asha has arrived sir.
Smell smell
perfume smell sir.
You and
I are full sir.
Congratulations sir on the fulfillment of your good intentions
.
[Music]
Hi Ashu, talk to me a little. Many more
happy returns of the day, my dear.
Thank you sir.
Sir, won't you give me any gifts for my birthday?
You'll have a surprise when you meet alone
.
Small or big?   No
small price, no big price, please
tell me right now,
sir.  Look over there,
sir.  Look here,
sir,
the lighting is good there.  Put on a
headband, tie a flower and a bow, and
go alone.
Sorry, sir.  Who takes photos in my office without asking me and then posts them? I don't like that. It's strictly a
profit-driven cut,
sir.
Why can't I even take a photo of you, sir
?  Won't you do this for me too
?  Go ahead, sir.
Otherwise, I'll take the correct date on my cell phone and
post it myself at the correct time.  Okay?  Okay, okay,
sir, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Can't you tell me anything clearly from the cake cake?
He's the one who said it, sir.  Look,
you're just like a girl, even a father.
I will wear sandals.   I keep up with
Dhoni's awesomeness.   Hold the
bow darling.
Sir, I can't fit a photo in there.
What do you want, sir?
Take a photo.   I'll take it
.  [Clearing throat]
Hey, isn't the light clean?  Hey, just relax
.  It's hard to drink light beer
.
Everyone, say cheese.
Sir, cut the cake here, sir, cut the cake here,
Asha, add [Applause] Asha, you sir, add, sir,
kiss Asha like that, sir,
Flo, tell me what you always do,
sir, stop the garden, turn off the lights,
now it's rude, just
stay like that, sir, what are you doing, sir, do you want to ask me
something, ask me,
why are you posting, why are you posting,
why are you shouting, please
[Laughter]
One dance, gold, birthday
celebration with my darling,
Asha, tag
Asha too, post it [
Scream] Baby, do you have a bad story, perform it
correctly,
hey, you bastard, Royapuram, Savakar, Petta, let's
take it like that, now watch,
Namaste, interview,
Namaste, interview, kirtana, Vasudevan, sadam,
Malaysia, Vasudevan, sado,
kirtana, Vasudevan, kirtana  Vasudevan
mam abi meeting me pisto
nothing understand actually sir is
from a national party to
join that [clears throat]
madam they were giving me a missed call
sir came from Delhi to see them
yaya
damatolaya traveling tired one second
sir
hey bhavach serialma toppal kodi vaa
moodudi hey
this is how India speaks India have
mfram delhi to meet you mam
fromm delhi yes
mam ok give
the phone to the mam sir
mam the line
hello i am manohar speaking
manohar which manohar
manohar that signal accident
oh you what do you want
no i have something important to
talk to you.
Do you have five minutes free?   I'm not a
full-fledged [clearing throat] I'm just a
Freya.  But
I don't want to see you.  [Music]
And one more thing, office right now
[Laughter]
What, baby, won't she come here herself?
Get out of my office, sir.
So, don't go out, you
idiots.   We can't do our
job in a place where there is no respect
.
Why are you all a friend?   I think
my friend Peeraja was the only one in this place
.  Did you know that Masa had an idea and
wanted to meet her
?   I don't have any
work to do with him, what kind of work is Gabbar?   What do you want
to talk to that girl about now? That's right.
Dhamma bi raja ki raja meenamma dilwale dunia bolaya tanya aach
aa aya anna nannam
Sir, my age is
okay, I have gone and played you very badly, sir, that's
true, sir, I have no forgiveness, sir, no forgiveness [laughter] What, I started crying, tell me not to cry, sir, he is a child, sir, no, I am really crying, see
[laughter] Is he
crying,
sir, tell me I have forgotten everything, let's
stop crying, tell me
everything, tell me,
no, I have forgotten everything,
what is your name, sir,
Lakshmana
Nipathi, don't forget anything, forget
everything that happened, don't
cry,
sir, when I
see you, do you look
like my father?
No, sir, he's like my little brother
.
Is the younger brother like the younger sister?
What's wrong?   You've got a fly in your
nose,
shouldn't you go?
You're the one who got the fly,
little brother. What's the matter? I'll have to
go upstairs and make you apologize right away.   Let's
see those.
They are sitting in the office, mad.   Don't
talk nonsense,
you've seen what's going on.   The earth is
hurting
[Music] Hey, what's happening,
sir? You're the one who drowned in your own tears. You
called and told me, sir.
It's better to see in my face. The bugs
are about the same.
What, you're like driving a flat tire on a lorry, didn't you
take a proper shower in the morning?
Look at the nettle, it's dripping with soap
.
No, that's a child's diaper.   Did you
throw it there because you were drunk?   Don't deviate from the topic
.  Who asked you to post a photo of Asha's birthday on
my cell phone without
asking
?
Sir, we asked you to do this.
When you were asking Asha to help you,
Asha was asking you to help her. When you were asking Asha to help you, Mano also asked, "Why don't you tell me
?"
Why are you shouting? I
thought you were asking where I would put the money.
Where did we put the money?
Don't know how to say Facebook?
Can't you tell me about my big deposit?
Oh,
okay, sir.  What's wrong with that now? Is there a
problem?
What's the problem,
hey Gunduway, are you looking very sexy today? Already ready to
play? You want one more?
Finish dinner, I'm ready.
I've got all the news.
Asha Bardhat knew.  What happened in the office, you know that,
Asha, she is very cute but very pretty.
Today is her birthday. I
went and
ordered a strawberry cake in the size of an order and cut it for her.
Amba took it. Did I take it? If that's all that happened, nothing
else will happen. Do you
know about the selfie matter?
I also wanted to take a selfie for that Kulfi
.  Then
I took seven or eight photos of this crazy guy.  Look at that, he left without
asking me
.  When will we correct the fear of the devil?   Is
that all that happened?  Nothing else is
happening?
I asked if he didn't go inside at all, or if that's all that happened, nothing else happened.
Asha, who always laughs and talks like a good joker, is always joking around
.  Without thinking, I
deposited ₹50,000 in his name.
How about 50,000 or not?   I had
that in my account.
You know everything about me.
Nanathan Pola Sa
[laughter] Ready, your time starts now. Ready, I've been
wanting to get this guy for a long time, darling.  S Come On, why are you
acting like a high school boy? Why are you
acting like an elementary school boy? The answer is no. I ca
n't say.  You won't let me tell you, sir, what is
honesty? Are you
calling the bank to tell me to go back to the kitchen?
No, darling, that Kumkuma serial,
Soumya.
Hello Soumya, I
was in a meeting with someone here about your work.   It's a
work matter, so it'll be
ready in a week or so.  Okay,
Mano, I don't need all this, I've already
committed to another big series.   I
called just to say that I have a better salary than this.  It's all because of you. It's okay, it's lost.
What's the point of calling your ex-boyfriend
Kirtan and making fun of him? You're a
joker. We
talked for a long time after we met and told him everything.  They also
forgot all about the fruits and
said all the best. You also met Kirtana madam and
asked for her help. Why is it that
you don't have any problems? It's for your own
good,
Soumya madam. The root has become clear for you. Don't just drink
it and go away. You should
do this free advice like the umbilical cord is removed. Then your shooting will have to come back
.
No, Mano sir,
what's wrong with that Kirtan, she
won't ask for your help? Should I go and
ask her for help? I think that's right too.
Darling, what's the matter
with that Kirtan,
why are you so scared to death?
What will she do? What will she do?
Manu,
where are you? Is there something wrong here?
Hey, how arrogant is that Kirtana girl?
You didn't apologize to your mother in time. You
told your mother everything.
That's important. Will you tell me?
You sent a notice from the court for Rs. 1 lakh for damages. Hey,
your manager asked Kutthalanjar for
Rs. 1 lakh. Mom, he asked his mother for Rs.
1 lakh. He didn't talk to her for 10 days because he was drinking tea.
Mom, what is the name of your accountant
?
Now, what's wrong with that?
Tell me, okay?
Kumaraswamy played the flute.
I thought about it when your account was wrong.  Is it 10 lakhs, 1 crore, 1 crore, a million, or
a million?
Both people were shocked at the same time, but
will the problem be solved?
Hey, our house is worth a crore rupees
.   We should
ask if it is our house's honor.
Oh Lord Muruga, let the local boy, Sellur
Raman, speak.  Why are you
talking irrelevantly now?  Are
you talking about that, Raja?  Do you want
this problem solved or not?  I
left you. Promise
your mother that you won't interfere in that Kirtan matter anymore
.  Stop, stop,
show me that hand for a minute.
I thought.  Don't swear
like a little boy who can't stand to be crossed,
swear like a grown man.   If
Mom did it,
who would be the lawyer?
Mr. Arjun Reddy.
The name itself is a myth, but the
person is even more so.
Hi, Asthala Reddy,
brother, I'll give you
two teas.
You've come in an ambulance.
Our Reddy is not
Reddy. My husband
Prakash Reddy,
I was just talking about that case. It's a little
late. What can we do? The car has another puncture. If he's
going to the ambulance tomorrow,
wherever he's going,
take my ambulance and take him there. He
said in Telugu.  Oh,
that's why I came to get an ambulance.
This is my
brother's case.
Brother, there is no case. Brother,
I told you, didn't I?
Hello, friend, don't worry about anything
. We can win this case.  You go and
organize the success party,
I'll go and wait for Paduva.   When
the hearing comes, I'm going to go and see him
.  Who is that Judge
Padmanabha, saying that?
Janjaya Nighne is saying something.   I was
so shocked by this, I just stood there and
laughed as I sang Arjun Reddy's dance.
Anna, all the best,
Mom. This is what we said at home.
As soon as I get a job, I'll buy myself a new tape
.  Are
there any new serials coming out on Sun Next? I'll watch them again.
Don't forget the tape,
Mom, Dad.
Hey Jasha Asmin,
Hey Mano
Asha Jasmine.
What a surprise.
How did you
come to this situation?  Hey,
how are you doing?   I
came to see HR Manager Balaji.  Interview.
Okay go straight first cabin all the
best mano.
Asha, this scoundrel, even the king, will
not pick up the phone.  You
talked to him about something.
I cut both of them off from Don't Talk About It.
That scythe is also very cheap.
Why did he misbehave?
I thought.  This stew is
made with tomatoes.  What did he do?   How did you
spend 50,000 on my birthday?   He
asks it again.  I see no conscience
.  Bloody Heartless Bellow.
I've been very disturbed ever since.
Oh,
I called you many times, but
you're the one who picks up [laughter]. No,
I'll come and talk to you after the interview
.   Are
you coming to Nightwalk?   I won't come, I'm
going home.  Oh, what is the HR
department doing here? Don't scold me, whatever I
ask.
Om Shakti [shouting]
This is not Sami, our councilor,
Vadakatthi Ramasamy.
Maruvathur himself
knows that he doesn't lie, so
why did Mike Om Shakti
get fired from his job? I've
come for an interview.  Why did you leave your job, Om
Shakti? Om Shakti? I didn't leave my job. Shakti,
why did you leave your job? Shakti.
Mr. P. Raja
present, Madam.   Is
Manu a close friend to you?   Not
only is your friend,
but you are also
terminated.  I'm the Terminator, get out,
Om Shakti,
how much sacrifices I've made for myself, if there was a
next life,
I'd have to take it as a hero, and you'd have to
take it as a hero, Brenda.  Only then will
you understand my difficulty.
Hey, I already had a hero friend, so
you just wanted to
be comfortable with that.  I
went to this interview straight away and looked for the HR manager's room and said, "Is it okay for
us to bribe the night manager?" When I got to the manager's room,
my friend Raja said, "Okay, he got the job
."  You're not even my friend,
sir.
Why did you lose your job, sir?
Why you are a dismissed by my boy Mr.
Mano in this company come on tell
me.
i won't give you asingagle reason you
know why because im terminating you
also.  What the hell is going on? Get out
.
Oh my God it's a medical miracle
first of all go to Banishtha interview another
we will not
speak English like actual
lunch morning dinner
sir I have requested this Asha Edisli nibody
sir is hiding outside sir sir sir is it like he went
somewhere to close the door come on me like a lot
wherever he
comes to us think.
He won't leave if you say it out loud
.  Why don't you try the Mind Voice
Slam, the money you put in and
the note you used to vote are not there? Is there
something wrong with your body?   No matter
how much you complain, I'll tell you
.
There is no history of whether he returned.  Why did
you ask for the 50,000 that Asha stole back, sir?
No, she's been getting
hit by my mother-in-law's dick every day without doing anything
.  That's why Asha asked me to
buy the 50,000 rupees that I gave her. Don't
talk loudly, Asha. Let's listen.  Asha
[clearing throat] Is she here?
Look, he's talking to token number seven.  Then we'll
ask her herself.   Let's not
talk about that big place anymore
.  Everyone who takes selfies should be careful
.  Come
here, please.  That's why you keep keeping the house, doesn't
Kalbrit know? Can you just leave it alone
?   Can you please tell me,
sir? What are you talking about with Sami like this?
Hey, I asked if you two could put in some paper. You've got a
good job
.  Then why don't you
go to the streets and post papers?
We are going to give the Rishi Ganesan
letter.
Why should I give a letter to Susi Ganesan?
That's Ramanuja's fault.  Is it a resignation
letter?
Why?
What did I do because of you?
Then you come and work, how can
she know, and then this
company will come and buy the lamp?
Then,
Anuchiruva beat the three ghosts with his shoe and left.  In the meantime,
we respectfully quit our jobs and went out,
boys.   I swear
on this samosa you bought me
.  All the problems she and I had were solved
.  The finish was
super darling, but now I've decided to make
love just because she hates me
.   The sandals are conformable
.
Why don't we go and herd cows in disguise
?  If you leave this,
there's a chance you'll find out that you'll do the same.  Shall we go to North India without talking and
join the Indian subcontinent?
What is he thinking?
Oh my gosh, gosh, gosh, I'm just having a one-
sided love affair.
Front side or back side?
Om Shakti Om Shakti.
Yes, is there a chance he will fall in love with her?   There's
no way he's going to call them.  This is where our love comes
out.
I said something that was not said, "
What's wrong with you?"
Dora Bhujji sir is coming.
Who is this Dora Phujji? She is
my favorite person to go to.
Dora Phujji, the
noise here is very loud. I will
come over and talk to her.
Now he's going to say "Who's that?"   The
dog itself would have told you both,
sir, sir, stop
I'm telling you,
Aussie Goose, get off, get off, get off, get off, get off, they're going to
Argentina, let's go
our other way, get off,
tell me the truth,
kid, get off, get off, get off,
we'll kill you, get off, get off, get off, get off, they're begging you, they're fainting, they're going to Argentina, they're going to
Argenta Hospital
.   If you're
confused, take it
out first.  Hey, let's tell you, hey,
what's wrong with me? Put that hand away and
tell me,
sir, they've fainted, sir.
What's wrong with you? Who's going to get
off the bus and pick up everyone? Hey,
pick up, I don't want you to talk, I'm going to put my hand on the floor and stop talking. Hey,
what's wrong with you?
We're just
sitting there like that.  Are you going to drop us off
?
Now, what should he not shout? Oh, yes, yes.
[Music]
Oh, you're the one who's gone, you're the one who's going to show up in an hour
.
One hour is hard.  He will be gone in 2 hours
.  If that doesn't work,
call 945471051.  I'll tell you what [music] to make
.  Hey, did you make a note,
you can't make a
note,
hey, do you know how to read
[music]
?   I
know.   Is
hair loss caused by medication?
If it is, say yes, if not,
say no.  Why are you acting like that
?
Who am I?   It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, let me
show you the mirror.
Kamala, Karnan, Kamesh Pratap, why are
you the only three people here?
Tell me, sir. Raja, do you want to
apologize to all three of you?
He doesn't want to apologize either.
Tell him that I have forgiven him.
Hey, we bought the AC just to apologize
.  If you go and buy it,
you will be fine. If you come back and beat it, it will be fine.  Do you want it?
Buy it.
No, does that eye have a license?
License?
Without a license, it's illegal.
We kidnapped him to become a commissioner, is that
legal?  Everything we do is illegal, as long as we get the money
.  [Music]
How much is the mark in dentistry?
I understand.  Don't ask for anything.  Adana
[music]
How long, sir?
Why don't you send them yet? If you ask me,
I'll
leave, sir.   Did
you see, Chattamara, that you came with your family and
these three people came all morning to
apologize and then protested leaving this station?
That's why
he's so stubborn. Where's the AC? Where's the AC?
[Music] He
threw that iron bar at me. Let's go to the
hospital. Let's
go in our car.
Hey, if you ask me, you've been
beaten up.
Kamala Kannan Kamesh,
why is he calling from the entrance of this temple? Come
here, I'll apologize.
Hey, Eruda, Eruda, brother, give me some, come back.
[Music]
Sir, Izhani [Music] Drink, sir.
Who are you?
I am Navani.   Is
Navani the
Prime Minister?
The girl's father, sir.
Drink up, sir.
This girl's name is Priyanka.  This girl was kidnapped last
Wednesday at 12:30 pm as she was leaving St. Francis Xavier
School
.
I think it's because I
tracked the cell phones of all the kidnappers in the city, and the
cell phone signal of the three of you was
near this girl's school
.  Then one of the three of you
kidnapped this girl
.   If you
truly confess to me,
I will put this kidney I took from you back inside.   I don't understand
.
I told you that I would put this kidney I took from you back in.
What is it?  How did you get your kidney?
What did you get?
Where did the kidney go?
What mobile wallets does the kidney not accept
?
Hey, you cow, don't you know what a kidney is
That's why there are two.  If one thing is wrong, then there is
another,
can't you adjust it?
Why is it that the alcohol we drink is not enough for four
kidneys?  If you have a kidney, you should
hit it with a hammer. [Music]
What are you playing? Silence, don't
be nervous like that.
The switch inside will go "tap tap tap"
.
Did you leave one?   If you leave
two more, you will die.   I don't
understand anything, sir.
They're making up for a mistake they haven't made in three days.
They blackmailed me by putting some sour candy on my kidney.   Don't be
afraid.   It's
very simple.  If you admit that you
kidnapped that girl, I will sew
your
beautiful heart back together.   Come back,
Thachituri, sir.
Well, you kidnapped a child from a poor family and gave it to a
rich family who were struggling without children.
Sir, many children have come from me and
are now millionaires.  Sir, I am doing this as a
service.
Kamarajarani Kammanati.  If you tell this to go out, they'll make
you a statue.
I do
n't know who this guy's two names are.  I'm not kidnaping.
Then prove that you didn't do it.
How?
What were you doing to your mother at that time [music]
?
Tell me the number of your grandmother who went to my grandmother's house to look after her.
I am speaking to your husband, Pratap.
If you know, do it and tell me.
I saw you on Wednesday afternoon
.   They
came and looked at me, wondering where I was
.
That's where.
Hey, you came and looked at me without knowing where I was
.
You too can live without a kidney for a week
This guy went to this guy and begged him to tell him to
bring the girl to the hospital
.  The girl who comes then is called
Dabakkun.
Hey, if you tell him that, he'll just tell you to shoot, you
loser
doctor. [Laughter]
Call them and tell them there's another girl
.
Tell them to come and buy it, and they will come.  [Laughter]
[Music]
Hello
brother, there is a girl.  I'm 10 or 11 years old
.  Are you buying?
The first one stabbed you again,
another girl. Looking at the speed you're going, it
seems like there's not even a girl in town,
you servant. You're no longer just a kidnapper, you're a
kidnapper.
Okay, I'll tell you tomorrow, come on,
okay,
I'm leaving even my kidney after 15 years in the service industry.
No, bro.  You have the
most experience in this matter.  So
until we get a girl [music],
stay with us.  May your kidney be with him
.  Is this Ivan available?
Hey, are you all kidding?
I told you that if you give me an idea, I'll give you my kidney back.  Did the kidney also
come and go and come up with an idea?
This is a big idea, Tiger. We are
looking for him.  Hey, I
was just shouting like this.  Lift your kidney and
blow into the caccus.
Blow on the cuckoo, you blow it, yeah
[sigh] There's another girl,
you're either there or there's no way
[music] I'll dress her up like a
doll.   Well, I
can pretend to be a lotus flower.
Sir,
leave it alone.  Wait, have
you practiced giving injections?
How can I do it again?
[Music]
Look carefully, sir.
One needle is correct. The
medicine is correct.
One two one that's it,
[ __ ] this, go away
[music]
Driver, driver, I
know this girl definitely won't girl.
What did you say, there is
only the letter, I want
to put flowers in it, please, my dear,
this is my moon, why do
you lie so awkwardly when I blow on the moon that I hit? What are you doing,
you are wrong, why are you beating him? He will
forget everything when you are beating him,
doctor, that girl is here,
doctor, ask where that girl is,
doctor.   I
don't have the girl, sir.  I've already given
my hand to someone else, sir.  Who is
near?
Hey, what's up, Moonji, this is
n't a business.   Wo
n't I become a business to
you?  I
can come to Tirusava to do business for you.
Bhagat just
looks at him.
Hey,
what the hell, just because I put a light on it, I tore it all apart with a knife and
put my kidney in a bottle.  Quiet, quiet
Sister, is that water too little?
Oh my,
what's wrong? They made it look like a blind eye
.  You said you would marry him, but
now no
one will marry you.
Look,
the doctor, you have made it so that even if you have this child, you will be
asked who you are
. Those who have studied are those who have studied.   It would
still be fine for 4 days.
Until then, who will watch my moon?
Who has ever listened to
[music]
Doctor, please give me that water.
I've been asking for an hour.
Put it on, doctor, doctor,
this is the plan.
This is what we are going to do.
The plan is very good, but the people are
all very poor
.
The doctor will perform an operation and leave, as time goes by.
[Sighs]
Anyone can catch all that.   Don't just
sit outside and do penance to protect your child.  He wo
n't agree to all that either.   I will
not agree.  I have to
say something he'll agree with.   It
takes a fool to agree with that.
[Music]
This is not your father. [Music]
You are not this mother's husband.
This mother is not that mother's brother-in-law. So
you are acting like a family and
kidnapping children.
[Music]
Oh, what's wrong with everyone there? Last week, there was a kidnapping and
then a car
accident.  Who is driving the car?   Do
you have knowledge?  There are so many ladies in the car, I
don't want to drive, Jagir.   Look, there's
a beautiful girl with a wound.
[Music] Please
beat this well and
get it out.  I won't go there many times
.  Okay, you've all
been beaten up, so go sit down.
[Music]
Okay, what can I do for you?
According to the information received by Sir, a Kowala
man has kidnapped many girls
.  If we had made our correct plan and
killed all those girls,
he wouldn't have been able to file a police complaint.
We have a problem too, Gummi.
The total worth of those girls is 50 crore
rupees.
The plan you're talking about has more
risk for us.  I
told you so.  It's a shame
they are the ones who work as wage laborers.  If you
go to these people and talk about a deal worth crores of rupees, they wo
n't be intimidated, they'll only end up killing you
.  A lion can only be killed by a sword
.  Even a child
can't scream in these forests.  You can show him the moonshines and make him lose his
child.  Hey,
you're wasting your time. It's my place.
Why?
Sir, please
[music]
I won't vote normally.